haha you kids are such a cheat now run
long to bed it's almost
midnight the sword B next year sa
Patrick's is until
tomorrow oh bro whatever you are doing
up there you better cut it out we're
trying to sleep down
here why aren't you talking to me I
swear you and Bart will be better not
secretly be having sex
again I am doing nothing of the sort but
Bart will be is here though yo man
what's up Bart letby go home if our mom
catches you she'll take away our fidget
Spinners but all we're doing is cuddling
my [__] is afraid of the dock yeah we
know people are trying to sleep in this
house what kind of sexual Savages do you
take us for the gay kind well if you
guys aren't making those tapping noises
then who is it sounds to me like it's
coming from the window maybe it's the
new Postman that's been checking out you
your butt Sonia what are you doing up I
can't sleep I thought I saw a sleep
paralysis demon at the door but then I
noticed it was just Uncle Chuck in his
Whitey ties checking you out for like an
hour he does that a lot for some reason
I was going to tell you weeks ago but
Uncle chck kept me quiet with gumdrops
I'm K my
mom it's a handsome little dude with a
box of Lucky Charms cereal was he the
one throwing things at our window oh
golly he's so tiny and adorable like a
plush boy are you stuck up there little
fellow I am not a plush toy and I
certainly no baby I'm a leprechaun I'm
going to hunt for me Po gold after it
was stolen when I pulled into the Panda
Express for some orange chicken have you
guys happened to come across gold coins
or misplaced rainbows
nearby what's all the commotion I can
hear you screaming all the way from down
the
hall there's a leprechaun outside and
he's throwing cereal at us make him go
away Mommy apricorn huh sure there is
kiddies whoever you are are there you
better get lost my son Sonic has his
boyfriend over and he's not afraid to
use him what the [__] there's nobody out
here I bet he was lying mother spank his
fat cheeks Sonic is this another one of
your tricks to avoid getting in trouble
for having bartab be over you don't have
to keep lying like this bartab is so
strong I can't physically stop him from
entering our home to pound your ass
regardless so I would hope you would at
least be honest with me I'm not lying
it's true Miss Hedgehog I fear for what
may have happened if I the most powerful
man alive wasn't here to keep a watchful
eye on his big ground behind well since
we're all awake we might as well go
check
outside hurry I smell something that
way look Hedgehog household there is
something smell at the base of the tree
yippi it looks like lime pudding don't
get ravenous yet bro that might be
stinky leprechaun
crap well I'll be it certainly does look
like it doesn't it Charles you don't
think only
on
y
That's then I'm afraid our greatest
fears have been realized there were
survivors after all from the great
leprechaun genocide the great leprechaun
genocide your uncle and I hoped we would
never have to tell you this story but I
think you're old enough to handle it
what is it mom why were the leprechauns
genocided well maybe it would be best if
your uncle explained it instead since he
was the one who accidentally did it I'll
read
kid you going to a story
about of magal
cryp yippi I love Uncle Chuck's [__]
up
stories boy boy nothing B going out and
exploring mobian Wilderness with me
and yeah it helps that we've all been
friends since childhood and that we red
blue and yellow we like the dull
versions of the primary
colors haha toothpick you're are very
funny it's no wonder why the three of us
have been friends all our lives now come
on it's not much further until we find
that really cool thing I wanted to show
you guys I wouldn't show anyone besides
you since you have been my best friends
since
childhood
we your
par I'm mentally
disabled are you
going what you don't trust me it's not
that of the and Ed up in for
mountains
then I would keep my app shut if I were
you now take a look at the good
[__] hot damn a't
she what
it's not just any Rock Charles that's a
leprechaun Rock apparently the
leprechaun store their magical powers in
green rocks when they're not using it
just imagine what someone could do if
they ever got their hands on one what we
could do the chaos we could
bring them e all this rup of our world
easy for you to say you were born in a
silver diaper but me and toothpick weak
have been made to live underground for
thousands of years with that power in
front of us I can save our people I
could do so much cool random [__] like
makan Island that floats in the sky or
some [__] where we can live away from
dangerous
predators he can't let
your and I won't let you stop me as
WIP what are you waiting for to pick the
again grab the stone and flee Apple are
you [__] gay Charles is our friend
and that doesn't belong to us if we take
it who knows what the leprechauns may do
to try and get it back that's right than
you and destroy your side think of your
family yeah [__] shut up toothpick
you're on the sex offenders registry
then you two better cut it out or I'll
show you why I'm on the
registry oh God
don't
let I'm trying but I can't run that fast
since I pulled down my pants God damn it
what was I
thinking at last with this power at my
disposal I can user the aid race into a
new
age oh
no
this
land and was the very
last after
that
started then how did you guys possibly
defeat them all what they had in
strength they lacked in numbers because
most lepre corns are homosexuals so they
rarely reproduced since a lot were
heterophobic by
Nature from for
example I don't get it Mr leprechaun if
you talked to us before why are you
hiding from us now I'm sorry it's
because I'm
[__]
and and I'm proud of it but my therapist
say I shouldn't be let him out of the
net
unle Domingo we can trust him I feel it
it's probably because we are both fun of
the color
green come inside and eat little dude
we'll help you find your pot of gold
after everyone has had a nice warm meal
oh boy can we watch the Disney Channel
original movie like of the Irish that's
my
favorite here you are one huge helping
of spaghetti with
preo oh
spaghetti what you got a problem with my
Mama's spaghetti [__] don't make me
have bleb your old me over there so I
can stuff your face in between my fat
cheeks and blast a huge wat of gas go on
and have a bite Sonic's mom makes the
best spaghetti I want to but the laws
clearly state in the greatly preown
Bible that we PRS can only eat foods
that are green or decorated in green if
you have some green sprinkles on hand I
could sprinkle on top why don't you
sprinkle on some parsley it's green and
it pairs really well with spaghetti
girl shut your bit ass up do I look like
I eat vegetables if you don't eat
vegetables then what green foods do you
eat Skittles so anyway when are we going
to find my pot of Cal well we were
planning on waiting until
morning oh is an
all Turn Down for
What wow did you just change night today
by snapping your fingers how did you do
that I'm a
leprechaun look there it is but that's
my best friend Knuckles house what makes
you think it's
there you're all being silly I'm sure
there is a perfectly reasonable
explanation for why there's a rainbow
shooting out of knuckle's
house sorry guys my grandfather says I
can't have anyone over today he doesn't
trust [__] on St Patrick's Day over
his fear of
leprechauns Knuckles close the door
there might be leprechaun outside
Knuckles is that a pot of gold behind
you no it sure looks like a pot of gold
to me well it's
not go
away Qui we don't have any green rocks
in this house now scram ather Knuckles
stole a leprechaun's pot of gold and we
really need to give it back can you talk
to him and persuade him to come out and
talk to us my great-grandson a thief I
am appal how dare you accuse my Angelic
son of thievery in his own home Knuckles
has always been the sweetest most
kindest boy who can do no wrong but he
has a cauldron filled with leprechaun
medallions
that doesn't prove [__] you are just
being a smelly
[__] Knuckles can you come over here
for a
minute what is it
great-grandfather Knuckles these kids
are telling me that you're stealing
money from endangered
species why no a there why would I do
that you taught me that stealing was
wrong that's what I thought you really
are the sweetest boy on this planet my
little red Twizzler don't feed into his
life old man that's the kid who beat me
up at panma
Express silence you you are a ginger so
you ain't got no soul God has given me
the Divine Right to Smite the cause St
Peter would never let you pass through
Vine ply Gates hey F knucker did you
know that according to Folklore you get
pinched on St Patrick's Day for not
wearing green who gives a [__] I got
green glasses glasses aren't
clothes leprechaun blast Turn Down for
What crap new piece of [__] I know just
the man to deal with
you well well well who would have
thought fate would once again bring me
to the Lucky Charms mascot no not you
why are you here Mr leprechaun do you
know Mindy's dad know him I can't get
that man's face out of my mind that man
killed my
father oh shut the [__] up it was his
own Papa that held a knife to my throat
first I only pooped diit into his mouth
because he tried to murder
me oh goody girls I think Daddy is
home
I'm back from work [__] make me some
[__] spinach
Puffs baby come quick our next door
neighbor stole a leprechaun's pot of
gold like a
badass thaton blast turn down for
what never mind my big sexy beef cake
why don't you step away from the window
and join me and the girls for some
delicious birthday cake I am afraid the
celebratory events are going to have to
wait my lovely ducky do the leprechauns
have commenced a full scale assault on
87% of mobus because somebody stole one
of their rocks for the first time in
over 10,000 years every country on Mob
have agreed to lay their differences to
rest so we can put down those feisty
midgets once and for all oh no what are
you going to do
what tells you worthless [__] doll I'm
going to kick ass but it's Mandy's 6th
birthday can it wait a few more hours no
also do you have any egg salad
sandwiches I can't take with me in case
I get hungry on the bloody
Battlefield no that's fine there will
probably be some MREs when I get out
there what's an M it stands for meal
ready to eat think of it like a bag of
food that can prepare itself so it's
basically like a woman but slightly
better okay well stay safe dear don't
tell me what to
do now hold at you two we don't have to
resort to violence it's a Patrick's Day
the most wholesome day of the year Bart
lebby is right you know the parade is in
town today why don't we all go there and
blow off some steam a bra I suppose I
can't put my thirst for Revenge to bed
right now maybe they're even selling
green corn
dogs oh wow it's beautiful I have never
seen so many people wear green in the
same place before pretty [__] and hub
our family comes here every year I I am
so turned on right now nobody look at my
crotch H look everyone there's another
leprechaun right over there how fun is
this that is not a Le it's Cal
appropriation is what it is a six foot
talk man and some cheap Halloween
costume look pal we're just trying to
have some fun fun would be giving me
back my pot of gold why are you yelling
at me for I didn't steal it hey you yeah
you're not a real
aicon oh yes I am you are the one who
was a fake ugly little man how does it
smell being downwind of my ass hey can
somebody get this drunk [__] out of
here you godamn poser I'll [__] kill
you what's happening to him why is he
[__] glowing I'm [__] dying if a
leprechaun remains separated from his
pot of gold for 2 hours he will cease to
exist well done if you told me that I
would have just given it right back do
you want to go back to my
house it's too late now My Sweet Summer
child it would take like 20 minutes just
to get back to your house it ain't all
bad on the bright side what bright side
[__] I'm funed on the bright side you
can finally be with all of the other
leprechauns in heaven the ones who lost
their lives during the Great leprechaun
genocide no when leprechauns get touched
by a human they are automatically denied
entry into heaven and get sent right to
hell and I was just punched in the face
but please honor one last request it's
been so long since I've seen a true
Irish F dance would you perform one for
me in the middle of the streets why
we're not
Irish come on sibs he may be dead but
that doesn't mean we can't have a little
bit of
fun
n
a